https://pichermitage.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
We do not collect personal information about you when you visit the web site unless you choose to provide it to us to take advantage of a specific service, for example completing an online form. Any information which you provide in this way is not made available to any third parties and is used by Hermitage Genetics only in line with the purpose for which you provided it.
If you choose to send us personal information, for example via the Contact Us email form, we will use that information to respond to your enquiry and will only pass your details to another agency if it is required by law or that agency is relevant to your enquiry. We do not collect personal information for commercial purposes.
Copyright
Material on this site is protected by copyright. The copyright owner is Hermitage Genetics. You may not make alterations or additions to the material on this site. Appropriate acknowledgement of the copyright owner is required if material is re-published in any format.
Disclaimer
All information on these pages is provided by Hermitage Genetics and is believed to be correct as at the time of issue. Hermitage Genetics accept no liability for any inaccuracies or any loss or damage arising from the use or reliance on information obtained from the website.
The Hermitage Genetics website links you to many other websites. We are not responsible for the content or availability of these sites.
UK AI Order Line:
08009 177302
IRL AI Order Line:
+353(0) 56 777 0011
Visit:
Newsletter Sign Up
Download Brochure
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site, you are consenting to our use of cookies.OkPrivacy policy
